Still, these Ishbalans are just refugees, right?
If Scar is among them,
then it's a different story.
Even if that's true,
isn't this a bit much?
Oh? Are you criticizing our superiors,
Sergeant Fuery?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Our ultimate objective
is to secure Scar.
It's likely that we won't
meet with any resistance.
But what if we do?
I mean, we have information that before we were posted there,
the Ishbalan refugees were attacked in Central by thugs who claimed to be the military.
I'm just saying, they may not have too much trust in the military.
Those markings...
Man cannot obtain anything
without first sacrificing something.
In order to obtain anything,
something of equal value is required.
That is alchemy's
Law of Equivalent Exchange.
At the time, we believed that
to be the true way of the world.
You...!
Zolf J. Kimbly!
How are you still alive?!
Kimbly?
The Crimson Alchemist?
A State Alchemist?
You were supposed to have been executed a long time ago
for your multiple violations of orders at Ishbal.
You can come right out and say it.
I indiscriminately made women and children go "boom."
And when my superiors
tried to stop me, they also went...
"Boom!"
I was certain I would be looking forward to an execution.
But for some reason,
I was kept alive.
Why?
Who can say? The gentleman standing there would know, wouldn't he?
How am I supposed to know?
How long are you going to allow this disturbance to persist inside the command center?!
Arrest them! Take them all into custody at once!
Yes, sir!
Sensei...
I told you, it's no use!
Please wait, Sensei!
All right, Al!
Magnificent!
He's a homunculus, all right.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Hold it!
She's magnificent too!
A superb transmutation!
But those who would dare lay a hand on the Führer...
must meet with defeat by
my own artful transmutations!
I wish you'd give me
some more credit.
I'm used to seeing muscles,
ones more handsome than yours.
Brother, if we don't stop those two fast, the whole building will be destroyed!
If they're not careful,
this town's going to cease to exist!
Brother!
Interesting body you have there, huh?
He caused an explosion
out of nowhere!
I've heard about this.
It's an alchemy where he transmutes the materials within a body into something similar to explosives,
then quickly contracts them
to create an enormous explosion.
Why are you interfering with us?!
We want that child too.
Besides, our boss has
some business with you.
Oh, is that right?
Just a second! Don't tell me you're planning to turn me into a bomb!
You mean I can't?
No, you can't!
Did Fullmetal tell you that that was his arm and leg?
Mm-hmm.
Then you passed through the doorway under your own power?
Doorway? Doorway?!
Whoa, now...
Starting today,
you're no longer alone.
Here,
eat these.
Come on.
Enjoy them well.
They've got several hundred human lives
packed inside them, after all.
Human...?
What's the matter?
You don't like them?
I see. Well, that leaves us with no other choice.
You can just return the arm and leg
that you took from him.
You can use alchemy, huh?
I get it, it's because of that arm and leg.
Listen, we're raised on
these stones of life.
We aren't human.
We're homunculi.
The fact that you can eat those...
means that you aren't human either.
Sure enough, we'll have to ask Greed-sama himself to step in!
Greed-sama!
Well, well, maybe I should
blow the whole building up.
I am Lt. Col. Frank Archer.
Crimson Alchemist.
It's a pleasure.
If you're here like this, then it must
mean that the Führer has agreed to it.
Or was this at Basque Grand's discretion?
Good question.
You have no intention of
returning to military duty?
I can make it happen.
Sensei! Sensei!
That bastard!
He scratched me good!
Major!
Ah, yow-ow-ow-ow!
This is bad!
I should have expected the master of the
Elric brothers to be able to take me unawares!
Thank you, Major.
I thought it might
turn out like this.
Your hand should be
on the other side.
This boy is no longer...
Go on now.
Do as you like.
Brother, it doesn't look like Sensei is here anymore.
Damn.
Why is she so caught up in that boy, considering the shape her body is in?
You two go around to the south! The rest of you come with me!
Let's go. We're trespassers here.
The Colonel's going to make more snide remarks about me.
What?
Verify that once again.
What is it?
Don't you know whether or not
the Führer is safe yet?
That's just it. When we contacted Central,
they told us that the Führer was not scheduled to come down south.
Impossible! We saw him with our own...
Have you taken the Elric brothers and that woman into custody?
No, I thought it was more urgent
to secure this crumbling building,
so I have returned.
Major!
No, it's all right.
Those two don't have anywhere else to return to besides the military, after all.
Just in case, have everyone look one more time for the Führer.
Yes, sir.
You know where Sensei is, don't you?!
Please, tell us. We're concerned about her condition.
What's more, that child is a homunculus, and there's no telling what he'll do.
The place where she performed human transmutation...
Izumi-san lost her child there.
She then transmuted his body, to try to bring him back to life.
How do you know that?!
I knew it.
She's gone to the same place this time. That's my hunch.
The place Sensei would choose...
Where she wouldn't do damage to the surrounding area...
Where no one else would go...
Yock Island.
That's it, right?
My son...
What's the matter?
Hurry up and do it.
Otherwise, I'll kill you.
Sensei!
Izumi-san!
Stop that!
Sensei!
You bastard!
Stop!
It's all right.
Sensei...
But that boy was going to kill you, Izumi-san!
I was planning to kill him.
But I'm the one
who should have died.
Why?!
I'm the one who created him.
I added some other materials to my dead baby's remains
and attempted a
human transmutation.
But what was born...
You know, don't you?
It wasn't... human.
When I came to, I was in front of the gateway once again.
Ed, what did you see on
the other side of the door?
Everything that is alchemy.
It felt as though all the reasoning
of the world was pouring into me.
The truth was in there.
The truth, huh?
To me, it looked like hell.
I placed the boy there.
But there's no way this boy could be that child.
I recognized him in one glance.
If he had continued to grow,
he would've been exactly the same age.
Most of all, for a homunculus to appear in this place,
it would have to be the boy
I left behind then.
He's a homunculus!
A man-made person,
something that somebody created!
Created?
Do you know how
homunculi are created?
No, we don't.
But it's probably the same way Chimera are created,
in places like the 5th Laboratory!
N—
No.
When worthless humans like you perform human transmutations for the hell of it,
what is born as a result
is a soulless reject,
furnished with only
a body and a mind.
That's what you guys
call a homunculus!
It couldn't be...
How do you know
something like that?!
I was forced to remember it, by Envy.
Envy? You've met with him?!
That's right.
Envy and all the others were born long ago,
thanks to some idiot somewhere performing human transmutation.
That's why we all
want to become human.
Shall we get going?
Well if isn't the Mightiest Shield.
Yo, Mightiest—er, was it "Monster" that you liked to be called?
Even after being locked away for a century,
it appears you still haven't learned, huh?
Yeah, you'll have to excuse me.
Was that joke too old?
I don't know any
present-day ones.
What happened to the skull?
I destroyed it, of course.
Is that right? You put it away someplace safe, huh?
Once I find it, I'll lock you away once again without delay.
As if I'd let you!
It appears that there really is a new member around here.
He's got nothing to do with you.
No, I would like to
go on living, after all.
I'm going to need
friends to do that.
You're late to the party.
Sloth...
Sloth? So, someone with that name
has been born, huh?
There's a new Lust as well.
That means that for the first time
in a while, all seven of us are around.
Pleased to meet you, Greed.
It is an honor to make
your acquaintance.
I may be greedy,
but I'm not stupid.
I have no intention of
fighting against two homunculi.
Oh, my.
We'll deal with him later.
Where's Wrath?
Ah, right about now,
he's with the Fullmetal boy.
You maneuvered him into a
confrontation with Edward Elric?
You were supposed to use Wrath to lure those two
toward the Philosopher's Stone once again, weren't you?
I wanted to see Fullmetal's—that dirty bastard's child's face tense with fear!
Everything—I remember it all!
On the other side of that door,
the only thing I could do was wait.
Just wait and wait...
Meanwhile, my body
grew bigger, little by little.
And then this one time,
a fool came by.
That fool came to leave
his arm and leg at the doorway,
shouting for his brother to be returned to him.
And so, I took that arm and leg.
And then, after another long while,
I opened the door.
I had finally come out of there!
It's not true...
Thank you for the arm and leg.
Thank you for the incomplete life.
I'm so thankful that no matter how much I might hate you, it's still not enough.
Now, give me all of your body!
Then I will become human!
That stung. I don't want your body.
Brother, if you're not
going to fight, then I will!
Al, stop! That boy isn't—
Still...!
This boy's right arm and left leg
belong to Brother!
He lost them for my sake!
Al...
The whole reason
we've been traveling...
is to get them back!
Fullmetal Alchemist...
Episode 32: "Dante of the Deep Forest"
Greed—
also known as the Mightiest Shield.
He is a homunculus.